ndrugs.com 2019-02-03

# Privacy Statement

**What’s our policy?  
**ndrugs.com is committed to protecting the privacy of its users and we have taken strong measures to ensure that the information we gather from you will be secure and confidential.

**What information do we need and what do we do with it?  
**If you join ndrugs.com, we will need your name, email address, city and postal code. We will use this information to contact you when a new development needs your support, or when we have new information important to our members.

**How do we protect your information?**  
We make sure that every online communication with our users meets our high standards of privacy and security. In addition, we take strong measures to protect all customer data against unauthorized access.

**Do we have "cookies"?**  
A cookie is a small information file stored in your browser and it recognises your device on future visits. No personal data is stored in our cookies. We use cookies to: 

  * Obtain statistical information about your general internet usage and learn how you and others use the Site, and to improve the Site and deliver a better service to you; 
  * Remember your session so that you can move from one page to another within the Site; 
  * Third party advertising and analytics cookies, which are placed by or on behalf of independent advertisers who are advertising on our site. These cookies may be placed within the advertisement and elsewhere on our site by us or by your browser. They are anonymous - they cannot be used to identify individuals, but they can also allow the advertiser or your browser to tailor advertising to you when you visit other websites using the same browser. They are used for statistical analysis by allowing the advertiser to count how many people have seen their advertisement or have seen it more than once, to make sure you are not repeatedly served with the same advertising messages. 

**Will ndrugs.com share any of my personal information?  
**Absolutely NOT! ndrugs.com will not trade, sell, rent of give your personal information to third parties without your consent. Access to the ndrugs.com email list is restricted to the two members within ndrugs.com who administer our Web site.

**Will ndrugs.com change its policy?  
**When you join ndrugs.com you consent to the collection and use of your information by ndrugs.com. If we alter our privacy policy in any way we will post those changes here so you can be aware of anything that may affect you in the way we disclose information.

**Any more questions?  
**ndrugs.com takes the issue of protecting your privacy seriously. If you have any concerns, questions, or just want to tell us what you think, feel free to contact us at [info@ndrugs.com](mailto:info@ndrugs.com)
